filez.com 2004-06-05

# Search the Web with YaKnow!

YaKnow Privacy Policy  
Smedstad Management Services, Inc. ("YaKnow") owns and operates the site located at http://www.yaknow.com. YaKnow is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its user community. The intent of this privacy policy is to detail the information YaKnow may gather about individuals who visit this Site, how that information is used, and YaKnow's disclosure practices. Please note that this policy applies only to YaKnow, and not to the Web sites of other companies or organizations to which we provide links.

Anonymous User Information  
YaKnow collects some anonymous information each time you visit YaKnow so we can improve the overall quality of your online experience. We collect your IP address, referral data, and browser and platform type. You do not have to register with YaKnow before we can collect this anonymous information.

YaKnow does not require you to share information that identifies you personally, such as your name or email address, in order for you to use YaKnow. YaKnow assigns an anonymous ID number to your requests and links the following additional data to that number: the date and time you visited YaKnow, your search terms, and the links upon which you choose to click. Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files to collect and store this anonymous user information. YaKnow analyzes the information to examine trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

Identifiable User Information  
From time-to-time YaKnow requests information from you that may identify you personally in addition to the anonymous information described above. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name, email address, mailing address, and zip code). YaKnow will not use or disclose your individual user information except as described in this privacy policy.

Tell Friend  
If you elect to use our referral service for informing a friend about YaKnow, we ask you for your friend's name and email address. YaKnow will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit YaKnow. YaKnow does not store the information related to your friends and the one-time email sent pursuant to your input will be our only contact with that person for such input.

Contact Us  
If you contact YaKnow, we may keep a record of that correspondence and we may collect your email address.

Third Party Information Gathering  
YaKnow includes content and ads from third parties that may perform user activity tracking other than that described herein. For more information about each third party content provider, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please refer to such third party advertiser's privacy policy.

YaKnow contains links to other sites on the Web. Please be aware that YaKnow is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by YaKnow.

Cookies  
YaKnow may set and access YaKnow or partner cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small data file that a Web site may send to your browser and which may then be stored on your system. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. For the session cookie, once you close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. 

Sharing Information  
Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a criminal investigation, a court order, or legal process served on our Web site. We may also share your personal information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of YaKnow's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. YaKnow may use third party service providers to serve ads and emails on our behalf. These companies may use technologies to measure the effectiveness of ads and emails and use information about your visits to YaKnow so that we can provide a better search experience to you. For this purpose, we may also provide these third party service providers anonymous information about your site navigation.

Notification of Changes  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement in places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

Children's Privacy (Users Under 13 Years of Age)  
In response to concerns about protecting children's privacy online, Congress enacted the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 ("COPPA"), which sets forth rules and procedures governing the ways in which Web sites may collect, use and disclose any personal information for children under the age of 13. In accordance with YaKnow policy and COPPA regulations, we DO NOT:

1\. Request or knowingly collect personally identifiable information online or offline contact information from users under 13 years of age; or  
2\. Knowingly use or share personal information from users under 13 years of age with third parties;

It is possible that by fraud or deception we may receive information given to us or pertaining to children under 13. If we are notified of this, as soon as we verify the information, we will immediately delete the information from our servers.

Questions regarding children's privacy should be directed to:   
Smedstad Management Services, Inc.   
52188 Van Dyke, Suite 208   
Detroit, MI 48310 USA   
\+ (1) 586.932.4097 phone   
\+ (1) 425.963.9017 fax   
Contact Us
